Guide to the Richard Wright Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Writings, 1933-1977; Series I; 38; (92 boxes)
  - BOOKS
    - Eight Men
      - Announcements and reviews - clippings, 1961 (Box 33, Folder 462)
      - Review from radio programs, script, 1961 Feb 9 (Box 33, Folder 463)
      - German translation, Der Mann, der nach Chikago ging
        - Publicity article from Claasen Verlag, 1961 (Box 33, Folder 464)
          [Including excerpt of "The Man Who Saw the Flood" and "How Richard Wright Found His Editor" in German]
        - Reviews - clippings, 1961-63 (Box 33, Folder 465)
        - Reviews from radio programs, scripts, 1962 (Box 33, Folder 466)
      - Reviews of French and Spanish translations - clippings, 1963, n.d. (Box 33, Folder 467)
    - "Escapee"
      - Outline, holograph, n.d. (Box 33, Folder 468)
    - "A Father's Law"
      - Draft, typescript carbon [with notes by Julia Wright], [1959-60] (Box 33, Folder 469-470)
    - "Island of Hallucination"
      - Five episodes prepared for publication in Soon One Morning, typescript carbon, n.d. (Box 34, Folder 471)
      - Draft, typescript, corrected, n.d. (Box 34, Folder 472-472d)
      - Draft, typescript carbon, n.d. (Box 34, Folder 473-473d)
      - Alternate draft pages, typescript carbon, n.d. (Box 34, Folder 473e)
    - "The Jackal"
      See: ARTICLES, etc. - "Urban Misery in an American City: Juvenile Delinquency in Harlem", Box 6, folder 148
      See: STORIES - "Rite of Passage", Box 87, folder 1062
    - Lawd Today
      - Background material - clipping (Box 35, Folder 474)
      - Early version
        - Draft pages, typescript carbon, [1936] (Box 35, Folder 475)
      - Late version
        - Working draft, typescript, corrected [with notes], n.d. (Box 35, Folder 476-477)
        - Final draft, typescript, n.d. (Box 35, Folder 478-479)
        - Final draft, typescript carbon, n.d. (Box 35, Folder 480-481)
        - Setting typescript, corrected, n.d. (Box 35, Folder 482)
        - Setting typescript, corrected, n.d. (Box 36, Folder 483)
      - Book jacket, [1963] (Box 36, Folder 484)
      - Advertisements and reviews - clippings, 1963-69 (Box 36, Folder 485)
      - Notice in Books-Across-the-Sea Bulletin, 1963 Apr-May (Box 36, Folder 486)
      - Reviews about French and Dutch translations - clippings, 1963, 1965 (Box 36, Folder 487)
    - The Long Dream
      - First working draft [episodes and notes], holograph, typescript, and carbon, corrected (Box 36, Folder 488-491)
      - Second working draft [Mississippi], typescript, corrected (Box 36, Folder 492)
      - Second working draft [Mississippi], typescript, corrected (Box 37, Folder 493-494)
      - Second working draft [Mississippi], typescript carbon (Box 37, Folder 495-497)
      - Intermediate draft [Fishbelly], typescript carbon with holograph and typescript, corrected sections (Box 37, Folder 498-499)
      - Intermediate draft [Fishbelly - concluding chapter], typescript carbon, n.d. (Box 37, Folder 500)
      - Late draft [Fishbelly], typescript and carbon (Box 38, Folder 501-504)
      - Late draft [Fishbelly], typescript and carbon, corrected (Box 38, Folder 505-508)
      - Later draft [Fishbelly], typescript, corrected, and carbon (Box 39, Folder 509)
      - Setting typescript, corrected, n.d. (Box 39, Folder 510-513)
      - Setting typescript, carbon, n.d. (Box 39, Folder 514-515)
      - Galley proofs, 1958 Jun 13 (Box 39, Folder 516)
      - Blurbs, typescript carbon, n.d. (Box 40, Folder 517)
      - Book jacket, [1958] (Box 40, Folder 518)
      - Advertisements - clippings, 1958-60 (Box 40, Folder 519)
      - Reviews - clippings, 1958-59 (Box 40, Folder 520-520a)
        See also: Oversize, Box 119, folder 1931
      - Fan mail, 1958 (Box 40, Folder 521)
      - German translation [ Die Schwarze Traum ]
        - Excerpt published in National-Zeitung Basel, 1960 Nov 13 (Box 40, Folder 522)
        - Reviews - clippings (Box 40, Folder 523-524)
        - Reviews from radio programs - scripts, 1960-62 (Box 40, Folder 525)
      - Clippings about Dutch, French, Italian and Spanish translations, 1960, 1963 (Box 40, Folder 526)
      - Play adaptation by Ketti Frings
        - Script drafts, n.d. (Box 40, Folder 527-529)
        - Announcements, advertisements and reviews - clippings, 1959-60 (Box 40, Folder 530)
    - The Man Who Lived Underground
      - "Long version"
        - First draft, typescript, corrected, n.d. (Box 41, Folder 531-534)
        - Early working draft, typescript, corrected, n.d. (Box 41, Folder 535-536)
        - Early working draft - opening scene, typescript, corrected, n.d. (Box 41, Folder 537)
        - Intermediate working draft ["Secret Song"], typescript, corrected, 1941 (Box 41, Folder 538-539)
        - Intermediate working draft ["The Man Who Lived Underground"], carbon, 1941 (Box 42, Folder 540-541)
        - Intermediate working draft ["The Man Who Lived Underground"], carbon, corrected, 1941 (Box 42, Folder 542-543)
        - Late working draft 1, typescript carbon, corrected with editorial notes, n.d. (Box 42, Folder 544-545)
        - Late working draft 2, typescript, corrected, n.d. (Box 42, Folder 546)
        - Late working draft 3, typescript, corrected, n.d. (Box 43, Folder 547)
        - Late working draft - opening episode, typescript and carbon, corrected (Box 43, Folder 548)
        - Late working draft - closing episodes, typescript and carbon, corrected (Box 43, Folder 549)
      - "Short version"
        - Drafts, typescript and carbon, corrected, [1944?] (Box 43, Folder 550-552)
      - Excerpts, typescript carbon, [1942?] (Box 43, Folder 553)
      - Announcements - clippings, 1942-51 (Box 43, Folder 554)
    - Native Son
      - Plans for work on Native Son submitted to the John Simon Guggenheim Memorial Foundation, draft, typescript, corrected (Box 43, Folder 555)
      - Background materials - clippings, 1938-39
        See: Oversize, Box 120, folders 1932-35
      - Clippings on racism and crime found with background materials, 1941-47
        See: Oversize, Box 120, folder 1936
      - Developmental draft material, holograph, typescript and carbon, corrected, 1938 (Box 43, Folder 556-557)
      - Developmental draft material, holograph, typescript and carbon, corrected, 1938 (Box 44, Folder 558)
      - Intermediate draft, typescript, corrected, n.d. (Box 44, Folder 559-562)
      - Late draft [incomplete], typescript, corrected, n.d. (Box 44, Folder 563)
      - Late draft, typescript carbon, corrected, n.d. (Box 45, Folder 564-568)
      - Setting typescript, corrected, [1939] (Box 45, Folder 569-570)
      - Setting typescript, corrected, [1939] (Box 46, Folder 571)
      - Galley proofs, 1939 Sep 20 (Box 46, Folder 572)
      - Illustrations by Clarence G. Hackett [ten block prints], 1942
        See: Oversize, Box 120a, folder 1936a-j
      - Book jackets, 1940-[43?]
        See: Oversize, Box 120, folder 1937
      - Publicity material, 1939-40 (Box 46, Folder 573)
        [Includes galley draft of Henry Seidel Canby's review for the Book-of-the-Month Club and postcard with notes by Wright]
      - Fan mail, 1940-75 (Box 46, Folder 574-578)
      - Clippings
        - Announcements, 1939-40 (Box 46, Folder 579)
        - Advertisements, 1940-42
          See: Oversize, Box 120, folder 1938
        - Reviews and notices, 1940-72 (Box 46, Folder 580-581)
          See also: Oversize, Box 120, folder 1939
        - Reviews and notices, 1940-72 (Box 47, Folder 582-588)
        - Reviews in German, Spanish, Swedish and Yiddish, 1940
          See: Oversize, Box 120, folder 1940
        - Letters to the Editor, 1940
          See: Oversize, Box 120, folder 1941
        - Bestseller lists, 1940 (Box 47, Folder 589)
      - Look Magazine photoessay on Native Son - clippping [fragment], with publicity material for radio stations, [1940] (Box 47, Folder 590)
      - Extracts from American reviews, typescript photostat, [1940] (Box 47, Folder 591)
      - List of reviews, typescript, [1940] (Box 47, Folder 592)
      - Reviews from radio programs, scripts, 1940 (Box 47, Folder 593)
      - Transcript of lecture by unidentified speaker, typescript, photocopy, n.d. (Box 47, Folder 594)
      - "An Unconscious Determinant in Native Son " by Frederic Wertham, offprints with clipping, 1944 (Box 47, Folder 595)
      - Excerpt published in PM Magazine, "If Bigger Wasn't Black and If He Had Money And If They'd Let Him Go to Aviation School, He Could Fly", 1941 May 7
        See: Oversize, Box 120, folder 1942
      - Serialization in The People's Voice, 1942
      - French translation, Un Enfant du Pays
        - Advertisement, 1947 Mai (Box 47, Folder 596)
        - Announcements and reviews - clippings, 1947-48 (Box 47, Folder 597-598)
          See also: Oversize, Box 120, folder 1942
      - German translation, Sohn Dieses Land, book jacket (Box 47, Folder 599)
      - Reviews of Dutch and Italian translations - clippings, 1947-48 (Box 47, Folder 600)
    - The Outsider
      - First version
        - First draft, typescript, corrected [with notes], 1947, 1952, n.d. (Box 48, Folder 601-606)
        - Early working draft, typescript, corrected, 1952 (Box 49, Folder 607-609)
        - Intermediate draft, typescript, corrected, n.d. (Box 49, Folder 610-612)
        - Intermediate draft, typescript, corrected, n.d. (Box 50, Folder 613)
        - Intermediate draft, typescript carbon, n.d. (Box 50, Folder 614-619)
        - Late draft, typescript, corrected [includes announcement of Spingarn Medal Award], 1952 (Box 50, Folder 620)
        - Late draft, typescript, corrected (Box 51, Folder 621-624)
        - Late draft - opening episode, typescript, n.d. (Box 51, Folder 625)
        - Setting typescript, corrected, 1952 Dec (Box 51, Folder 626-627)
        - Setting typescript, corrected, 1952 Dec (Box 52, Folder 628-630)
      - Second version - "Cross Daeman"
        - Early draft, holograph and typescript, corrected (Box 52, Folder 631-634)
        - Late draft, typescript, [1947] (Box 52, Folder 635)
        - Introductory section, holograph, n.d. (Box 52, Folder 636)
      - Autobiographical statement for book jacket, typescript carbon, 1953 (Box 52, Folder 637)
      - Book jacket, [1953] (Box 53, Folder 638)
      - Clippings
        - Advertisements and reviews, 1953 (Box 53, Folder 639-641)
          See also: Oversize, Box 121, folder 1943
        - Review in Swedish, 1953 Mar 31 (Box 53, Folder 642)
      - French translation - L'Intrus [by Guy de Montlaur]
        - Draft, typescript, corrected, 1954 (Box 53, Folder 643-644)
        - Review [as Le transfuge ] - clipping, 1956 Jan 20 (Box 53, Folder 645)
      - Spanish translations, El Extraño and De la Inocencia y la Pesadilla, reviews - clippings, 1956 (Box 53, Folder 646)
      - Swedish translation, Utanför
        - Book jacket, n.d.
          See: Oversize, Box 121, folder 1944
        - Clipping - review, 1956 Dec 1 (Box 53, Folder 647)
      - Dutch translation, De Buitenstaander
        - Review - clipping, 1954 Oct 23 (Box 53, Folder 648)
        - Radio program review, script, 1958 Aug 24
      - Norwegian translation, Vidnet, Clipping - review, 1954 Sep
      - German translation, Der Mörder und die Schuldigung
        - Clippings - reviews, 1966 (Box 53, Folder 649)
        - Radio program reviews, scripts, 1966 (Box 53, Folder 650)
    - Pagan Spain
      - Letters of introduction for Wright from Tolá Cuevas de Vera, Clifford Forster, Aurelio Valls and Unidentified [with note on addresses], 1954 (Box 53, Folder 651)
      - Outline, typescript and carbon, [1954] (Box 53, Folder 652)
      - Background material and notes (Box 53, Folder 653-654)
      - Photographs of Spain [69 prints and 18 negatives of religious processions and candid shots of Spaniards - taken by Wright or purchased as souvenirs], [1954] (Box 54, Folder 655-657)
      - Photographs of Spain - contact sheets [30 prints], [1954] (Box 54, Folder 657a)
      - "Raw Material of Impressions of Spain" typescript, corrected, 1954-55 (Box 55, Folder 658-661)
      - "Raw Material of Impressions of Spain" typescript carbon, corrected, 1954-55 (Box 55, Folder 662-665)
      - Early developmental draft, holograph and typescript, corrected (Box 56, Folder 666-670)
      - Late developmental draft, typescript, corrected, n.d. (Box 56, Folder 671)
      - Intermediate draft, typescript, corrected, n.d. (Box 56, Folder 672)
      - Intermediate draft, typescript, corrected, n.d. (Box 57, Folder 673)
      - Late draft, typescript, n.d. (Box 57, Folder 674-676)
      - Late draft, typescript carbon, n.d. (Box 57, Folder 677-679)
      - Final draft, typescript, corrected, n.d. (Box 58, Folder 680-683)
      - Final draft [fragment], typescript, carbon, n.d. (Box 58, Folder 684-685)
      - Blurb, draft, typescript carbon, n.d. (Box 58, Folder 686)
      - Book jacket, 1957 (Box 58, Folder 687)
      - Fan mail, 1957-60 (Box 58, Folder 688)
      - Clippings - Reviews, 1957, 1960 (Box 59, Folder 689-690)
        See also: Oversize, Box 121, folder 1945
      - Reviews in Spanish and Swedish - clippings - reviews, 1958, n.d. (Box 59, Folder 691)
      - German translation, Heidnisches Spanien
        - Clippings - advertisements and reviews, 1958-60 (Box 59, Folder 692)
        - Darmstädter Blätter: Wir lesen für sie review - clipping, 1963 Aug (Box 59, Folder 693)
        - Radio program reviews, scripts, 1958-60 (Box 59, Folder 694)
        - Photograph of book display at Frankfurt Book Fair [1 print], 1958 (Box 59, Folder 695)
      - Clippings about Dutch and French translations - reviews (Box 59, Folder 696)
      - Untitled article in Spanish [fragment], n.d. (Box 59, Folder 697)
    - Savage Holiday
      - First draft, holograph, [1952?] (Box 59, Folder 698)
      - Early developmental draft [fragments], holograph, n.d. (Box 59, Folder 699)
      - First developmental draft, holograph and typescript, corrected (Box 59, Folder 700)
      - Second developmental draft, typescript, corrected (Box 59, Folder 701)
      - Drafts of title pages, typescript, n.d. (Box 59, Folder 702)
      - Intermediate draft, typescript, corrected, 1953 (Box 59, Folder 703-705)
      - Setting typescript, corrected, [1953] (Box 60, Folder 706-708)
      - Setting typescript, carbon, 1953 (Box 60, Folder 709-711)
      - Final draft, typescript, n.d. (Box 60, Folder 712-713)
      - Final draft, carbons, n.d. (Box 61, Folder 714-716)
      - Synopsis by an unidentified writer [in French], typescript and carbon (Box 61, Folder 717)
      - Reviews [in Dutch and English] - clippings, 1970, n.d. (Box 61, Folder 718)
    - Tarbaby's Dawn
      - Background material - clipping (Box 61, Folder 719)
      - Early draft, typescript, corrected, n.d. (Box 61, Folder 720-721)
      - Late draft, typescript [with critical comments], n.d. (Box 61, Folder 722)
      - Late draft, typescript [with critical comments], n.d. (Box 62, Folder 723)
      - Late draft, typescript carbon, n.d. (Box 62, Folder 724-726)
      - Draft fragments and notes (Box 62, Folder 727)
    - 12 Million Black Voices
      - Book drafts
        - Early draft, holograph, n.d. (Box 62, Folder 728)
        - "First draft," typescript, corrected, 1941 Jan (Box 62, Folder 729)
        - Intermediate draft, typescript carbon, n.d. (Box 62, Folder 730)
        - Late draft, typescript, corrected, n.d. (Box 62, Folder 731)
        - Setting typescript, corrected, n.d. (Box 62, Folder 732)
        - Galley proof, corrected, n.d. (Box 63, Folder 733)
        - Notes, 1938, n.d. (Box 63, Folder 734)
      - Chapter drafts
        - Foreword, typescript, corrected and carbon (Box 63, Folder 735)
        - Chapter 1, "Our Strange Birth," typescript and carbon, corrected (Box 63, Folder 736)
        - Chapter 2, "Inheritors of Slavery," typescript and carbon, corrected (Box 63, Folder 737)
        - Chapter 3, "Death on the City Pavements," typescript and carbon, corrected (Box 63, Folder 738)
        - Chapter 4, "Men in the Making," holograph, typescript and carbon, corrected (Box 63, Folder 739)
      - Book jacket, 1941
        See: Oversize, Box 121, folder 1946
      - Fan mail, 1942-56 (Box 63, Folder 740)
      - Clippings - Announcements, reviews and advertisements, 1941-63 (Box 63, Folder 741)
        See also: Oversize, Box 121, folder 1946
      - Radio discussion of book by John T. Frederick and Arna Bontemps - program, 1941 Nov 18 (Box 63, Folder 742)
      - Condensed version for in Coronet
        - Preface, typescript, corrected and carbon, [1942] (Box 63, Folder 743)
        - Published version, 1942 Apr (Box 63, Folder 744)
    - Uncle Tom's Children
      - Preface, drafts, typescript corrected, 1936 Jun (Box 63, Folder 745)
      - Title leaf of draft "To be sold only for the cause of Loyalist Spain", photocopy [with explanatory letter from Thomas Brown Wilber], 1938, 1976 (Box 63, Folder 746)
      - "Bright and Morning Star," draft fragment, typescript (Box 63, Folder 747)
      - "Down By the Riverside," drafts, typescript, corrected, 1936, n.d. (Box 64, Folder 748)
      - "Fire and Cloud," drafts, typescript, corrected, [1936] (Box 64, Folder 749)
      - "Long Black Song," drafts, typescript, corrected, [1936] (Box 64, Folder 750)
      - Book jackets, [1938-40?] (Box 64, Folder 751)
      - Fan mail, 1942-48 (Box 64, Folder 752)
      - Advertisements from Story magazine, 1938 (Box 64, Folder 753)
      - Advertisement form letter from Book Union, n.d. (Box 64, Folder 754)
      - Clippings
        - Announcements, reviews and advertisements, 1938-65 (Box 64, Folder 755-760)
          See also: Oversize, Box 121, folder 1947
        - Reviews from Russian publications with transcripts in English [one translated by Paul Robeson, Jr.], 1938 (Box 64, Folder 761)
      - Announcement for enlarged edition, [1940] (Box 64, Folder 762)
      - French translation, Les enfants de l'oncle Tom, clippings - announcements, reviews and advertisements, 1946-48 (Box 64, Folder 763)
      - Adaptation for German radio program, script, 1961 Mar 12 (Box 64, Folder 764)
    - White Man, Listen!
      - Chapter drafts
        - "Why and Wherefore..." [Introduction] drafts, typescript, corrected and carbon, 1956 Dec 26 (Box 65, Folder 765)
        - "Psychological Reactions of Oppressed People" [Chapter 1]
          - Developmental notes, typescript, corrected, n.d. (Box 65, Folder 766)
          - Early version [from lecture], drafts holograph, typescript, corrected and carbon (Box 65, Folder 767-768)
          - Late version, typescript and carbon, corrected (Box 65, Folder 769)
          - German translation by Margot Schrepfer [incorporating parts of "Tradition and Industrialization"], typescript, carbon, 1962, n.d. (Box 65, Folder 770)
          - Lecture in Norway - pamphlet, announcement and clipping, 1956 (Box 65, Folder 771)
          - Lecture in Norway - poster, 1956
          - See: Oversize, Box 121, folder 1948
        - "Tradition and Industrialization" [Chapter 2]
          - Early drafts [from lecture], typescript and carbon, corrected and mimeograph, 1956 (Box 65, Folder 772)
          - Late drafts, typescript, corrected and carbon (Box 65, Folder 773)
        - "The Literature of the Negro in the United States" [Chapter 3], drafts, holograph, typescript and carbon, corrected (Box 65, Folder 774)
        - "The Literature of the Negro in the United States" [Chapter 3], drafts, holograph, typescript and carbon, corrected (Box 66, Folder 775-776)
        - "The Miracle of Nationalism in the African Gold Coast" [Chapter 4], drafts, typescript, corrected and carbon (Box 66, Folder 777-778)
      - Book drafts
        - Form letter requesting permission to reprint copyrighted material - drafts, typescript and holograph, corrected, 1957 (Box 66, Folder 779)
        - Permissions statements, drafts, typescript, corrected and carbon, [1957] (Box 66, Folder 780)
        - Final draft, typescript carbon, n.d. (Box 66, Folder 781-782)
        - Promotional material [statements], typescript, corrected, n.d. (Box 66, Folder 783)
        - "To French Readers" statement, typescript carbon, 1959 Feb (Box 66, Folder 784)
        - Book jacket, [1957]
          See: Oversize, Box 121, folder 1949
        - Clippings - reviews and advertisements [in English and Swedish], 1957-59 (Box 66, Folder 785-786)
          See also: Oversize, Box 121, folder 1949
        - Publicity letter from Doubleday compiling comments by Southern reviewers, 1957 Dec 3 (Box 66, Folder 787)
        - Dutch translation, Blanke luister toch! - book jacket with review and advertisement - clippings, 1963 (Box 66, Folder 788)
        - French translation, Ecoute, homme blanc - invitation to signing with reviews and advertisements - clippings, 1959-60 (Box 66, Folder 789)
          [transcript of review from Les Beaux-Arts includes cover letter from Boris Litvinoff]
        - Spanish translation, Escucha, hombre blanco!, clipping - review, 1960 Feb (Box 66, Folder 790)
  - FILM SCENARIOS
    - "Freedom Train" or "The World Between"
      [co-written with Audrey Davenport]
      - Outline drafts, typescript and carbon, 1951 (Box 67, Folder 791)
    - "Last Flight"
      [co-written with Crosby George]
      - Outline drafts, typescript and carbon, corrected (Box 67, Folder 792)
    - "Lucy Comes Marching Home"
      - Outline drafts, holograph and typescript, corrected (Box 67, Folder 793)
    - "Melody Limited"
      - Early version ["Jubilee"] outline draft, typescript, corrected, n.d. (Box 67, Folder 794)
      - Early working version ["Freedom's Song"] script draft, typescript, corrected, n.d. (Box 67, Folder 795)
      - "First rough running narrative draft," typescript and carbon [includes synopsis titled "The Idea"] (Box 67, Folder 796-797)
    - "Native Son" [adapted with Pierre Chenal]
      - "Synopsis of the film treatment," draft, typescript, corrected, n.d. (Box 67, Folder 798)
      - Scenes synopsis drafts, typescript and carbon, corrected (Box 67, Folder 799)
      - Developmental script draft, holograph, typescript and carbon, corrected, [1949] (Box 67, Folder 800-801)
      - Early script draft sections, typescript, corrected, [1949] (Box 68, Folder 802-803)
      - Intermediate script draft sections, typescript, corrected, [1949] (Box 68, Folder 804)
      - Late script draft sections, typescript, corrected, [1949] (Box 68, Folder 805-806)
      - Shooting script sections, typescript carbon, [1949] (Box 68, Folder 807)
      - Notes for script drafts, n.d. (Box 68, Folder 808)
      - Costume directions, drafts, n.d. (Box 68, Folder 809)
      - Note regarding film scenes, n.d. (Box 68, Folder 810)
      - List of codes for names and messages (Box 68, Folder 811)
      - Screen test by Richard Wright
        See: Series III, Personal Papers - Box 115, folder 1821a
      - Photographs
        - Publicity shots and photos of film set, including Richard Wright on S.S. Uruguay and cast party [64 prints and 1 negative], 1949-50 (Box 68, Folder 812-814)
        - Scenes from movie [84 prints], 1949-50 (Box 68, Folder 815-818)
        - Portrait photos of actors [22 prints], 1949-50 (Box 68, Folder 819)
      - Notes on film contract, n.d. (Box 69, Folder 820)
      - Plot synopsis [in German], typescript carbon, 1950 Jul 26 (Box 69, Folder 821)
      - Press release [in Spanish], 1949 Oct 11 (Box 69, Folder 822)
      - Receipts
        - From Inez Cavanaugh for coaching of Richard Wright, 1948 Dec 6 (Box 69, Folder 823)
        - From Pierre Chenal for interests in film, 1950 May 2
      - Plaintiff's brief - Classic Pictures vs. The Department of Education of the State of Ohio, n.d. (Box 69, Folder 824)
      - Programs, [1951] (Box 69, Folder 825)
      - Exhibitor's Campaign Book with Bulletin, [1951]
        See: Oversize, Box 121, folder 1950